LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Today, Jenoman military adviser and leader
of the democratic revolution, Marcelo Jarti,
was attacked and assassinated in Panan.
The incident occurred at the hotel he
was staying at with the advisory group.
Judging by the scale of the
attack, he is thought to be dead.
The leader of the democratic
revolution and a legendary hero...
He commanded many battles against
guerilla groups alongside the President,
and guided the country to a successful revolution.
He is a man of merit.
However, after the revolution,
he showed no interest in politics.
He believed that he was just a
soldier supporting the President.
He was said to be leading many
revolutions in neighbouring countries.
He miraculously survived 5 assassination
attempts made by the SAS and DELTA,
and was thought to be an invulnerable
hero in his own country...
He's coming out... It's him.
Inspector, scan.
Walking pattern, cyborged from both knees down.
The way he unconsciously strokes his cyborged right arm
is clearly a symptom of a phantom limb,
and is a strong physical characteristic indicating the existence of a ghost.
Some other behaviour patterns match the databank of the
European Police, identifying him as Marcelo Jarti.
The legendary hero has been
entering the country repeatedly?
Togusa, I'll follow Marcelo.
Switch with me in 13 minutes.
Got it.
Regarding the assassination attempt on Jenoman
Military Adviser Marcelo Jarti reported earlier,
the government has officially
declared that he is alive and well.
Although according to the official report by the
government, Marcelo suffered an injury to his right arm...
Everyone's being fooled by a double.
This is the sixth assassination attempt.
It's just that the targets were all fakes...
Is there any proof that the one
that the Major's following is real?
It can't be proven; it's a matter of probability.
Does the data that the inspector
dug up identify him as the real one?
That is also a matter of probability.
Argh, too much trouble,
just ghost hack him and make it all clear.
Togusa is following Marcelo's
taxi from the airport.
We should be hearing from him.
Locate his hideout first.
Put it under 24-hour surveillance.
Marcelo has entered this country twelve times, almost
once every five months over the past five years.
The Police Department seems to have noticed it,
but the foreign affairs section
was unaware of his actions.
So they came to us?
Yes.
They want us to find out why Marcelo
is entering our country so frequently.
Any possibility that it's because
he's the drug king of South America?
It's hard to imagine that Marcelo would risk
coming here by himself just for a drug trade.
Japan, where cyberbrain drugs are mainstream, is not an
attractive market for Marcelo who deals in natural drugs.
If he's the real one,
let's just take him down ourselves!
Because of interference from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
we have to let him go home peacefully this time.
Damn...
Major, I've located Marcelo's hideout.
Where?
New Port Hotel.
He switched cars 6 times, and settled down here.
Pazu, Bouma, go to the New Port Hotel.
Togusa, wait there.
Bouma? How is it?
Nothing for now.
I looked through the Hotel's guest list,
but there are no guests with the name Marcelo.
He got off the elevator on level 33.
There are VIP rooms there...
Welcome.
Batou! You ready?!
Ya, ya, anytime!
You like high places, right?
Yup, yup.
I certainly do like high places.
He's there. Marcelo is.
There are a few other visitors.
Hm? I hear a cart coming.
A Maid Robot's coming.
Good, I'll borrow her eyes then.
Are you sure we won't get traced?
I won't screw up.
Room service...
Marcelo...?
Comparing with Marcelo Jarti's data... matched.
Ishikawa, look up the man with Marcelo.
Doing it already.
Got it.
Kanekichi Gondou, a member of Kourinkai,
leader of the Niihama Section.
You can definitely call him the central figure.
He controls almost all of the
cyberbrain drug flow in Japan.
Kourinkai practically owns this hotel too.
This is the Police. Gondou's inside, isn't he?
I need to have a talk with him.
Will you open the door?
We have no business with cops. Go home.
Don't touch me punk.
Chief, what's this?
Hold on, I'm looking.
What do you want, fucker?!
Major, the cops taking action in the hotel are Prefecture
Police trying to raid the scene of a drug trade.
They're after Gondou, not Marcelo.
If the Prefecture Police get
Marcelo, it'll screw things up badly.
Help Marcelo escape.
It might get a little rough.
I'm aware of that.
Got it.
Batou, we're going down.
Damn it... We have no choice.
We have to hurry to our usual spot.
You guys, hold the cops here.
Bang!
They sure were messy...
I'm finished. The c-c-cops are on to me...
I-I-I'm finished...
This is Togusa, I'm following Marcelo.
Roger that.
In 8 minutes, Pazu and Bouma will take over.
Chief, could you find out how many
facilities Kourinkai has in the prefecture?
Also, could you check for videos of Marcelo around the
capital back from when he first entered the country?
Okay, retrieve all camera data for
the past five years of Marcelo...
All the facilities that Kourinkai possesses too.
Major, I'm sorry.
I let him escape.
Bouma!
I got him.
I got them.
Over the last five years,
there are some video records of Marcelo Jarti
from the service area of the freeway that
goes to the mountains outside of Niihama.
Comparing it with the behaviour pattern of Marcelo,
we can pick up some of Kourinkai's facilities.
I'm sending the data now.
A huge warehouse...
I have some weird data on the warehouse.
Every time Marcelo entered the country,
there were dates when the electricity
usage was abnormally high.
Electricity usage...?
This is Bouma.
Marcelo has left his car and
has got on to the roadway.
I'll have the Tachikoma continue the chase.
There it is.
Image from the Tachikoma...
Bingo!
Marcelo and Gondou are in there.
Hmm, there aren't that many guards either.
This is Togusa, I'm in the back of the warehouse.
Alright.
As soon as Ishikawa takes control of the
facility's lines, we're going to detain Marcelo...
We're going in!
I'm finished, huh?!
Hello!
Sweet dreams!
Major, did you hear him?
I've found him. It's him.
"Major, did you hear him?"
"I've found him. It's him."
So this jamming of the radio waves is the reason
behind the noise in the communication system...
Togusa, where are you?
Hm? It's that...
Togusa, can you hear me?
"Attack on my mark!"
Roger!
Batou! Marcelo's in the plant. Follow me.
Huh? What? I can't hear you, Major?
No good... Togusa, go!
Roger!
Freeze!
Major? Where are you?
Togusa, what's this all about?
There are two Marcelos!
Huh? What are you talking about, Major?
I've already caught Marcelo.
Hold on...
What's going on?
I've caught Marcelo, too...
Ghost Dubbing Device...
Walking pattern, cyborged from both knees down.
The way he unconsciously strokes his cyborged right arm
is clearly a symptom of a phantom limb,
and is a strong physical characteristic indicating the existence of a ghost.
Some other behaviour patterns match
the databank of the European Police,
identifying him as Marcelo Jarti.
He says he's real...
Really?
The Chief said not to let any
organisation know, but is that ok?
It's a global scandal.
Tell them Marcelo himself is already dead?
But what a South American stud!
He endured ghost dubbing 3 times!
Kourinkai was scared of retaliation
when Marcelo finally died.
They somehow continued dubbing
without the country noticing.
It was convenient to mass-produce doubles,
but then they needed to synchronise the doubles' memories...
Yes, they couldn't allow individual differences, and they
had to make everyone believe the real one was alive...
So that was the reason for the sightseeing trip...
I still don't understand what circumstances
made them take such a huge risk.
That's because he's a hero, right?
What will happen to the citizens, when they
find out the hero they admire is a doll?
A doll that continues to speak of dreams is slightly better
than a dysfunctional hero in name only.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up